<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Liang Rui</title>
    <link>https://liangrui.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Liang Rui</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 22:38:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://liangrui.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Plan</title>
      <link>https://liangrui.github.io/blogs/plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 22:38:14 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://liangrui.github.io/blogs/plan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-plan-in-five-years&#34;&gt;My Plan in Five Years&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;study&#34;&gt;Study&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Work hard to learn the knowledge in class, especially try my best in the courses I am good at. In the remaining three years, I will work hard to get on the Dean&amp;rsquo;s Honor Roll just like I did in my freshman year.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While maintaining the current GPA, work hard to improve it, preferably to 3.8 or above. Must be in the top 35% of my major every year to receive a renewal of my entrance scholarship.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Travel Plans</title>
      <link>https://liangrui.github.io/blogs/travel-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 22:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://liangrui.github.io/blogs/travel-plan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-travel-plans&#34;&gt;My travel Plans&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have traveled to many countries and constantly expanded my horizons. I have been to Asia（including Japan, South Korea, Singapore, Thailand, the Philippines, Malaysia）, Europe（including the United Kingdom, France, Switzerland, Germany, Italy）, the United States, and Australia&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I‘d like to go to a Nordic country. I really want to see the scenery there with my own eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2025, my parents and I plan to visit another city in the United States that we have not been to. At the same time, I want to visit my good friend who I have been with for more than ten years and is now studying in Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Gallery</title>
      <link>https://liangrui.github.io/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://liangrui.github.io/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A volunteer experience</title>
      <link>https://liangrui.github.io/blogs/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 22:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://liangrui.github.io/blogs/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;volunteer&#34;&gt;Volunteer&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On November 24, 2024, I volunteered at the Guangdong-Hong Kong-Macao Road Cycling Race and the 15th National Games Road Cycling Test Race. This is my first time to volunteer at a large-scale event since I came to Macau. I followed the organization and was mainly responsible for cheering for the players at the entrance and exit of the Macau section of the Hong Kong-Zhuhai-Macao Bridge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through this volunteer activity, I met some new like-minded friends and learned a lot. The security preparations for the event were quite sufficient, and communication between departments during the competition was also extremely important.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
